First gentleman: I say! This Old Interest 'victory' parade is
cue-2
the best show I've been to in quite some
time! Ha! That's what I call 'An Election
cue-3
Entertainment'!
Second gentleman: Absolutely! And when our side
cue-4
challenges the result in parliament, it
can only end one way. Parliament is full
cue-5
of New Interest supporters – we've got the
majority there! When there's
cue-6
disagreement over the result of an
election, it's parliament that has the
cue-7
final say!
First gentleman: Yes, quite! And then this 'True Blue
cue-8
Triumph' will vanish into thin air as if it
never was! Let's enjoy the spectacle
cue-9
while we can!
cue-10
The Duke: Indeed!
cue-11
It's just as you say. Friends in high
places, just like me, the Duke of
cue-12
Newcastle – that's what counts. How does
the saying go? 'The
cue-13
ambitious Peer, the Knight, the 'Squire, can
buy the election they
cue-14
desire'. So reflect, my friends, and judge
from thence, How
cue-15
idle this extreme expense; What mighty
sums are thrown away,
cue-16
To be the pageant of the day!